# LIZ KOVALCHUK

## Web Developer

#### **ABOUT**

Trained as a classical musician, I apply inherent understanding of structure, complex pattern recognition and logical symbolism into my code. My experiences as an artist and performer enhance my ability to ensure that my work has a cohesive narrative, great user experience and impeccable attention to detail.

#### SKILLS & TOOLS

HTMI 5 Visual Studio CSS/Sass Git & GitHub

JavaScript

**APIs** PHP Webpack Visual Studio .NET (MVC) SQL **Firebase** React Laravel

Angular WordPress

#### **EDUCATION**

Humber College 2017-18 Post Graduate Certificate Web Development

Ball State University 2012-14 Masters in Music

Roosevelt University 2008-12 Bachevlor of Music

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

Simplistics Web Design Full Stack Developer and Project Manager

September 2018 - February 2019 Maintained code for hangit-up.com and limor.money. Created custom WordPress plugin for simplistics.ca to display google reviews upon contact form submission. Supervised 8-9 developers and 2 designers while managing 20-30 projects in queue.

Simplistics Web Design Full Stack Developer Intern

Summer 2018

Developed igfmining.org using WordPress in team of three. Built assemessment system for upplift.co using gravity forms and custom built WordPress plugins.

### **SELECT CONTRACTS**

Humber College Web Developer for International PM department 2018-2019

Built custom application, an alumni network (ipmpalumninetwork.ca)

New York Session Symphony Orchestra Musician Contractor

2016-2017

Managed professional musicians.

**Networks Touring Production Company** 2014-2016

> Beauty & the Beast International Tour Principal Cellist

#### CONTACT

lizk.ca 416 254 7530 hello@lizk.ca

